{"_id":{"$oid":"5dd3796dd2dfaaa776485b1f"},"question":"Shahrukh Khan's First film with karan johar?","answer":"kuch kuch hota hai","choices":["dilwale dulhaniya le jaenge","kuch kuch hota hai","kal ho na ho","trimurti"],"difficulty":"H","weight":30.0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dd3796dd2dfaaa776485b20"},"question":"Shahrukh Khan's First Film as a Producer?","answer":"phir bhi dil hai hindustani","choices":["dil se","josh","ashoka","phir bhi dil hai hindustani"],"difficulty":"H","weight":30.0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dd3796dd2dfaaa776485b21"},"question":"Shahrukh Khan's Date of Birth?","answer":"2 november 1965","choices":["2 november 1965","5 november 1965","25 december 1965","2 november 1963"],"difficulty":"H","weight":30.0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dd3796dd2dfaaa776485b22"},"question":"Shahrukh khan's first film?","answer":"deewana","choices":["deewana","baazigar","darr","anjaam"],"difficulty":"E","weight":10}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dd3796dd2dfaaa776485b23"},"question":"Shahrukh khan's first television apperence?","answer":"dil dariya","choices":["fauji","dil dariya","circus","kon banega crorepati"],"difficulty":"E","weight":10}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dd3796dd2dfaaa776485b24"},"question":"Shahrukh Khan's IPL team?","answer":"kolkata knight riders","choices":["Chennai Super Kings","royal challenger bangalore","rajasthan royals","kolkata knight riders"],"difficulty":"E","weight":10.0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dd3796dd2dfaaa776485b25"},"question":"For which film Shahrukh Khan got first filmfare best actor award?","answer":"baazigar","choices":["yes boss","baazigar","anjaam","darr"],"difficulty":"M","weight":20.0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dd3796dd2dfaaa776485b26"},"question":"Shahrukh Khan's wife's name?","answer":"Gauri khan","choices":["kajal khan","kajol khan","khajel khan","gauri khan"],"difficulty":"E","weight":10.0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dd3796dd2dfaaa776485b27"},"question":"Rahul Khanna is the name of Shahrukh Khan Character in which film?","answer":"kuch kuch hota hai","choices":["kabhi khushi kabhi gham","kuch kuch hota hai","kal ho na ho","yes boss"],"difficulty":"H","weight":30.0}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5dd3796dd2dfaaa776485b28"},"question":"Shahrukh's fathers name?","answer":"taj mohammed khan","choices":[],"difficulty":"M","weight":20.0}
